■
本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 翻译制作
更多美剧更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
《反恐24小时》前情提要
Previously on 24
杰克
Jack.
把枪放下  快点
Put down your weapon. now!
怎么回事
What the hell's going on?
-莱恩·伯内特在哪儿  -什么
Where's ryan burnett? what?
迈尔参议员的办公室主任  他在哪儿
Senator mayer's chief of staff-- where is he?
托尼从他的线人口中
Tony double-backed to one of his contacts
得知有第二次袭击
Who gave him information of a second attack.
一个小时内就会在华盛顿发动袭击
It's gonna take place here in washington within the hour.
朱玛的手下正在行动
Juma's operatives are carrying it out.
伯内特一直在暗中支持他们
Burnett's been supporting them all along.
他知道下次袭击的地点  所以
He knows where the attack's gonna take place, so you can
如果你不告诉我他的下落  我就自己找
Either tell me where he is, Or i will find him myself.
伯内特先生  你是个叛国者  恐怖分子
Mr. burnett, you are a traitor and a terrorist.
我不是
I am not.
我爱我的祖国
I love my country.
鲍尔先生  我是泰勒总统
Mr. bauer, this is president taylor.
目标在哪儿
Where's the target?!
你的所作所为已经触犯了法律  鲍尔先生
What you're doing is against the law, mr. bauer.
我命令你收手
I am ordering you to stand down.
在哪儿
Where's...?
把鲍尔先生带走  他被逮捕了
Take mr. bauer away. he's under arrest.
你本该先来找我的
You should have come to me.
你本该先来报案的
You should have presented your case.
就算报告给您  又有什么分别呢  阁下
And would it really have made a difference, ma'am?
杜巴库上校已经死了
Colonel dubaku is dead.
永远不能让劳伦特知道这件事
Laurent must never know about this,
还有他父亲是个懦夫
Or about his father's cowardice.
我父亲不见了
There is no sign of my father.
让我取代他在突击队的位置吧
Let me take his place on the assault team.
果真是虎父无犬子啊
Spoken like a true dubaku.
劳伦特  我们该出发了
Laurent, it is time for us to go.
这就是了  拉里  绝对没问题
This is it, larry, no question.
他们出动了
They're moving out.
知道下个目标是什么吗
Any idea what the next target is?
不知道
No.
从我们的位置
From our location,
到入口大概有100米的距离
It is approximately 100 meters to the entrance.
本字幕由YYeTs人人影视翻译制作
更多美剧下载 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译：nana    帝释天   aiai    lighthouse
时间轴：shawnliu87    校对：何何  非燕   Nil
■
后期：冰河     总监：何何
以下事件发生在晚上7点到8点
The following takes place between 7 p.m. and 8 p.m.
行动
Let's move.
够了  我现在就要见她
That's it. i need to see her right now.
泰勒女士  总统一有空就会见你的
Ms. taylor, the president will see you as soon she is able
那你告诉她  她女儿不想再等了
Well, you tell her her daughter is done waiting.
我现在去医院陪我父亲
I'm going to the hospital to be with my father.
我想在你走之前
I think it would be a good idea
还是去跟她说一声为好
To talk to your mother before you do that.
总统有令  让你继续留在白宫
The president's orders are that you remain in the white house.
那么如果我想走
So if i try to leave,
你会对我施行人身限制吗
You will actually physically restrain me?
不会那样的  泰勒女士
Oh, that would never happen, ms. taylor,
因为我知道你对你母亲
Because i know you have too much respect
还有她的工作给予了足够的尊敬
For your mother and her office
绝不会做得太离谱
To ever let things get that far.
算你说得好  探员
Well done, agent.
你干这行有好长时间了吧
You've been at this a while.
五届政府  女士
Five administrations, ma'am.
奥莉维亚
Olivia,
你母亲让我告诉你发生了什么事
Your mother asked me to fill you in on what's happening.
恕我直言  伊桑
Well, with all due respect, ethan,
她派你来传话是大错特错了
You're the last person she should be sending.
城内将会有另外一起恐怖袭击事件
There's about to be another terrorist attack on this city.
所以她才让你继续留在这里
That's why she wants you to remain here.
你是说会有更多飞机会失事
Are we talking about more planes going down?
还不清楚
We don't know.
但是不管会发生什么  都已是迫在眉睫了
But whatever's going to happen will happen soon.
我要去五角大楼了
I'm heading to the Pentagon.
最重要的是
On top of all of this,
还有一个进兵计划需要处理
There's also the invasion to deal with.
所以  记住
So, bear in mind,
你母亲正面临巨大的压力
Your mother's under tremendous pressure right now.
媒体知晓安全措施加强之事
It's only a matter of time before the media picks up
只是个时间问题
On the heightened security measures.
我要在他们知晓之前
I want to issue a statement
发布一个声明
Before that happens.
对袭击的现实可能性进行淡化处理
Play down the actual likelihood of an attack,
告知媒体安全措施
Talk about the security measures
只是出于必要的考虑  而避免谈及...
as being due diligence, rather than...
不  梅瑞狄斯
No, meredith.
公众有权了解实情
The public deserves the truth.
我们需要强调谨慎和冷静
We stress caution and calm,
但是我们必须承认情报显示
But we acknowledge we have intel
我们正面临着又一起恐怖袭击
about another terror attack
是的  阁下  安吉拉和我
Yes, ma'am. angela and i will have something
会尽快为您起草演讲稿
For you as soon as possible.
总统阁下  拉里·莫斯打来电话
Madam president, larry moss is calling in.
他说有关于袭击的线索
He says he's got a lead on the attack.
电话接过来
Put him through.
莫斯探员  已为您接通总统阁下
Agent moss, you're on with the president.
总统阁下  我们发现
Madam president, we've discovered
并确信在波托马可河南岸
What we believe was a staging area
有一处集结待命地区已被恐怖分子占用
Being used by terrorists on the south shore of the potomac,
此地就靠近ITP铁路和船厂
Near the itp rail and shipyards.
总统阁下  我们已经确认当中一名男子
Madam president, we've identified one of the men
就是朱玛将军
As general juma.
什么
What?!
朱玛在华盛顿
Juma's in dc?
是的  阁下  就我们所掌握的情况
Yes, ma'am, and we know that there are at least
至少还包括另外12名恐怖分子
A dozen other men involved in the attack,
他们全副武装  准备发起一场小规模的战争
And they are armed for a small war.
有没有发现任何关于
Have you found evidence that tells us
袭击目标的证据
Where the target might be?
没有  阁下  但我们已派出搜查小组
No, ma'am, but we have search teams
找寻这伙歹徒的下落  我们希望
Out looking for the men, and we're hoping that
沃克探员能掌握更多线索
Agent walker has more information.
是她发现的朱玛  但是
She's the one who i.d.'d juma, but, uh,
我们和她失去了联系
We've lost contact with her.
失去联系
Lost contact?
是的  总统阁下
Yes, madam president,
但我们有足够的理由相信她还活着
But we have every reason to hope that she's still alive
还在继续追踪恐怖分子
And in pursuit of the terrorists.
如果她在那儿  阁下  我们会找到她的
If she's out there, ma'am, we'll find her.
不许动
Hold it right there!
我是蕾妮·沃克探员  联邦调查员
I'm agent renee walker, FBI.
沃克探员  我们刚刚接到搜寻你的警报
Agent walker, we just got an alert on you.
你们得马上打电话给
you need to call larry moss
联调局的拉里·莫斯  告诉他们
At fbi right now. tell him there's gonna be
会有一场针对白宫的恐怖袭击
A terrorist attack on the white house.
好的  长官  我现在就打给他们
Yes, ma'am. i'll call it in right away.
我是汤普森
this is thompson...
巡警汤普森  请报告你的位置
Ranger thompson, please respond and report your location.
巡警汤普森
Ranger thompson...
比尔
Bill.
司法部长希望把你转交到他手下羁押
The attorney general wants you transferred to his custody
这样他可以对你提出刑事诉讼
So he can file criminal charges.
有没有任何袭击的消息
Have we learned anything else about the attack?
我跟托尼联系上了
I reached tony.
他从线人那里得不到半点情报
He couldn't get any more information from his guy.
据联邦调查局说
According to the fbi, renee walker
蕾妮·沃克独自追踪线索
Followed a lead on her own
来到波托马可河边一个废弃的仓库里
To an abandoned warehouse on the potomac.
发现了一支以朱玛为首的
Got a visual on a heavily-armed commando unit
全副武装的突击队
Led by juma himself.
但是在她汇报完之后  就失去了联系
But she went missing right after she called it in.
失去联系是什么意思
What do you mean, missing?
还不确定
We're not sure.
联邦调查局正在搜索那一区域
The fbi's searching the area,
但是还没有任何她的踪迹
But there's no sign of her, or any evidence
也没有关于目标的线索
Telling us what the target might be.
伯内特知道
Burnett knows.
总统以赦免他为交换条件
The president offered him an immunity deal.
他拒绝了  什么都没说
He turned it down, hasn't said a word since.
该死  比尔  他要开口的时候我被拦住了
Damn it, bill, he was talking when they stopped me.
把我和他关在一个屋子里  给我5分钟
Put me in a room with him for five minutes,
我们能阻止阴谋得逞的
And we can stop this thing from happening.
杰克  就算我愿意放了你
Jack, even if i was willing to release you,
他也已经被送去肯尼迪医院了
He's being transported to kennedy memorial.
你根本无法接近他
You couldn't get access to him.
好吧  那你去
Fine. then you do it.
你能接近他
You can get access.
我没受过高压刑讯技术的训练
I'm not trained in coercive techniques.
这件事是板上钉钉的
This is not a maybe.
莱恩·伯内特是恐怖分子的同伙
Ryan burnett is an accessory to a terrorist attack.
如果你坐以待毙  无辜百姓就会性命不保
If you don't do this, people will die.
我不想跟你争论该做什么
Look, i'm not arguing about what needs to be done.
我不会干  也不想干  那不是我的风格
But i can't do it. i don't do that. it's not me.
-这不是个好理由  -杰克
- That's not good enough. - jack!
该死  比尔  这不是个好理由
Damn it, bill. that's not good enough.
是你告诉我冷眼旁观的人
You were the one who told me, people who stand by--
等同于密谋袭击的帮凶
They might as well help them plant the bomb.
你能行的
You can do this.
比尔  你必须干
Bill, you have to do this.
我做不到  杰克  对不起
I can't, jack.I'm sorry
比尔
Bill?
我做不到
I can't.
就是这了  将军
This is it, general.
我们在管道的另一边
We're on the other side of the conduit.
你到位了吗
Are you in position?
是的  将军
Yes, general.
准备好了
I'll be ready for you.
怎么了
What was that?
我以为你说话了
I thought i heard you say something.
我自言自语呢
Just, uh, talking to myself.
对了  我跟你说了周六
Yeah. hey, i tell you we're having people over
我们来几个人搞个派对
On saturday?
没什么特别的  就是带点中国菜
Nothing fancy. we're bringing in chinese.
这回你能去吗
You think you're gonna make it this time?
中国菜
Oh. chinese.
但我还是想吃希拉做的饭
But i was looking forward to sheila's cooking.
搞定  将军
All clear, general.
干得好
Excellent.
10秒钟后  我们就能进入
We'll have access in ten seconds.
一旦进入里边  在附近的报警器
Once we're in, we'll have two minutes
报警之前我们有2分钟的时间
Until the proximity alarms come back up.
Five,
4  3
Four, three,
2  1
Two, one...
行动
Move!
我已进入特勤局追踪网络
I've accessed the secret service tracking grid.
她在哪
Where is she?
就在总统办公室里
Right here in the oval office.
出发
Let's go.
安全
Clear.
我们可能会遇到抵抗
We will meet resistance,
并且必须悄无声息  速战速决
which we must counter quickly.Silently.
距离下一次
We have nine minutes
特勤局例行通话还有9分钟
until the next secret service roll call.
我们必须在这之前找到总统
We must find the president by then.
那会澄清那件事
That will clarify that.
没错  一旦准备好发布
Yeah, I'll let you know,
我就会通知你
as soon as it's ready for release.
放下电话
Let go of the phone.
距例行通话还有5分钟  将军
Five minutes until roll call, general.
朱玛派人杀了你父亲
Juma had your father killed.
什么
What?
听着  我知道杜巴库是你父亲
Listen to me, I know that Dubaku is your father.
朱玛一直在骗你
Juma's been lying to you.
你父亲死了
Your father is dead.
我爸活着
My father is alive!
朱玛必须杀人灭口
Juma had to make sure that your father didn't talk.
所以他派一个叫乌铎的人杀了你父亲
So he sent a man named Udo to murder him.
不  不  我不相信你
No. No, I... I don't believe you.
乌铎杀他的时候我就在场
Look, I was there when Udo did it.
我跟踪他上了轨道车才找到了你
That's how I found you. By following him back to the rail car.
朱玛将军背叛了你
General Juma betrayed you.
你在撒谎  你在撒谎
You are lying. You are lying!
蕾妮
Renee!
我知道攻击目标了
I know the target.
请重新签发押送犯人的授权书  长官
Reissued warrants and order for transport, sir.
很抱歉  杰克
Sorry, Jack.
这边走  鲍尔先生
This way, Mr. Bauer.
-我是比尔·布坎南 -我是拉里·莫斯
Bill Buchanan. It's Larry Moss.
蕾妮·沃克说袭击目标是白宫
Renee Walker says the target is the white house.
情报可靠吗
How good is her intel?
很可靠  她说他们是从地下管道进入的
Firsthand. She says they're getting in via subterranean access.
我会启用安全屋
I'll initiate a lockdown.
你去调遣紧急事件反应小组
You alert CIRG.
我是比尔·布坎南
This is Bill Buchanan.
我已确认  白宫成为恐怖袭击的目标
I have confirmation the white house is a target of a terrorist attack.
红色警戒  保护总统
Condition red. Secure the president.
各就各位
Get to your posts.
杰克  我需要你的帮助
Jack, I could use your help.
我要确定你会按我说的做
I need to know you'll do exactly as I say.
我保证
You have my word.
总统在哪
Where's the president now?
在总统办公室
Oval office.
-怎么了  -您得跟我们来
-What's the meaning of this? -You need to come with us.
-白宫遇袭  -什么
- The white house is under attack. - What?!
总统阁下  我们得走了
Madam president, we need to go.
女士  我们现在就得走
Ma'am, we need to go right now.
泰勒女士
Ms. Taylor.
我已找到总统女儿
I've got the president's daughter.
正赶往安全屋
We're on our way to the lockdown.
有探员受伤  没有安全的出口了
Men are down. There's no safe path out.
我们必须把她送到一层的安全屋
We need to secure her in the first floor lockdown.
比尔  这边安全
Bill, we're clear.
-他在这儿干嘛  -他是我的人
- What the hell is he doing here? - He's with me.
总统阁下  目前你需要一切能得到的援助
Madam president, right now, you need all the help you can get.
怎么会这样  我的女儿呢
How is this happening? Where's my daughter?
亚伦·皮尔斯正将她带往安全屋
Aaron Pierce is taking her to lockdown
我们得走了
as we speak, but we need to move.
五区  七区  九区的探员  听到请回答
Agents in zones five, seven and nine, please respond.
五区  七区  九区  请回答
Five, seven and nine, respond.
无法联络到信号区内的探员
I can't reach anyone in the quadrant.
朱玛的人马直奔我们而来
Juma's men are headed straight for us.
他们知道总统在哪
They know where she is.
他们在追踪总统  比尔
They're tracking her, Bill.
总统阁下  让我看看您的追踪器
Madam president, let me see your tracker.
比尔  安全屋最近的通道
Bill, what's the most direct route
-怎么走  -从东边走
- to the lockdown? - From the east.
我会带着追踪器去西边  引开他们
I'll head west with the tracker and draw them away.
您跟着杰克
You go with Jack.
鲍尔探员
Agent Bauer.
这是你的地盘  我跟着你
This is your house. I'll follow.
我们正护送总统去安全屋
We're moving the president to lockdown.
霍维斯探员  多个区域都有探员遇袭
Agent Hovis, we've got agents down in multiple quadrants.
我们需要增援  长官
We need reinforcements, sir.
收到  我们正去往安全屋
Copy that. We're on our way to the lockdown now.
上
Let's go.
将军
General.
总统离开了办公室
The president has left the oval office.
她正朝西边走廊走去
She's heading down the west corridor.
乌铎  带你的人去那边
Udo, take your team that way.
我们两面夹击
We'll trap her in between us.
我们离总统越来越近了  长官
We're getting close to the president, sir.
在前面  绕过这个弯儿
Up ahead, around this corner.
总统的追踪器  长官
The president's tracker, sir.
他们知道我们来了
They know we're here.
他们正把总统送往安全屋
They're moving the president to the lockdown.
找到她
Find her.
带上他  我们需要人质
Take him. We need hostages.
把他们押到一起
Start gathering 'em up.
行动
Let's move.
我们在去安全屋的途中遭遇敌人火力
We've engaged hostiles on the way to the lockdown.
我们没看到总统
We do not have a visual on the president.
我们还有两分钟路程
We're still two minutes away.
起来
Get up!
起来  起来  起来
Get up! Get up! Get up!
快走  快走  快走
Move it! Come on! Come on, move it! Come on!
亚伦  我是杰克  我和总统在一起
Aaron, it's Jack. I'm with the president,
正去安全屋  你在哪
approaching lockdown. where are you?
我们还在楼上  杰克
We're still upstairs, Jack.
快走
Move! Move!
敌人已占领了这个楼面
Hostiles are in control of the area.
我正在考虑如何绕过他们抵达安全屋
Looking for a way past them to the lockdown.
收到  朱玛的人正在逼近
Copy that. Juma's men are closing on our position.
在30秒内你必须赶到
You're going to have about 30 seconds to get here
-不然我就要封门了  -明白
- before I have to seal this door. - Understood.
我女儿不来不许你关门
You will not close this door until my daughter gets here.
总统阁下  现在您的性命高于一切
Madam president, right now, your life is the priority,
由不得您 请进屋
whether you like it or not. Please, step inside.
总统阁下  您还好吗
Madam president, are you all right?
亚伦  我是杰克
Aaron, it's Jack.
我们已经在安全屋内
We're sealed off in the lockdown.
我们遇到袭击  别无选择
We came under attack. We didn't have a choice.
反正我们也无法到达了  杰克
We couldn't have made it anyway, Jack.
我们会试着找条路出去
We'll try to find a way out of the building.
收到  亚伦
Copy that, Aaron...
杰克
Jack.
杰克  听得到吗
Jack, do you read me?
亚伦  我是杰克  听得到吗
Aaron, it's Jack. Do you copy?
妈的  朱玛切断了我们的联系
Damn it. Juma's cut off our communication.
我必须确认我女儿的安全
I need to know that my daughter's safe.
总统阁下  我还无法确保这点
Madam president, I can't answer that yet.
安博
Abo.
朱玛将军
General Juma,
他们的增援来了
They brought in reinforcements.
我不知道
I don't know how much longer
我们还能守住多久
we can hold them off from your position.
原地待命
Stand by.
盖兹
Ngozi?
探员正从四面八方赶来
Agents are moving in from
敌众我寡  实力悬殊
all directions; we will be heavily outnumbered.
探员们知不知道 总统在安全屋里
Does secret service know the president is secured in the lockdown?
唯一一个看见的人已经死了
The only ones who saw are dead.
把我接通到他们的通讯频道
Put me on to their communications channel.
说吧  长官
Go ahead, sir.
我是朱玛将军
This is general Juma.
我抓住了总统
I have the president.
立即撤退  否则我就杀了她
Evacuate immediately, or she will die.
我需要确认总统在你手上  才能下令撤退
I need proof you have the president before I can give that order.
-让我们和她通话  -你是谁
- Let us speak to her. - Who is this?
霍维斯探员
Special Agent Hovis.
Agent Hovis,
把你的人撤出白宫
Move your men out of the building
撤出警戒线  不然我就杀了总统
and beyond the fence line, or I will kill the president.
而且她的死会算在你头上
And her death will be on your head.
霍维斯探员
Agent Hovis?
我们正在撤
We're pulling back.
所有探员  立即撤退
All agents, fall back immediately!
重复  所有探员撤退
I repeat：all agents fall back.
将军  特勤局正在撤退
General, secret service is retreating.
他们正在撤  将军
They are retreating, general.
所有人都撤了吗
All of them?
是的  长官
Yes, sir.
把所有人质带到这儿来
Gather all the hostages and bring them here.
-封锁出口  行动  -遵命  长官
- Lock down the exits. Move. - Yes sir.
确认西区探员正在撤退
Confirming secret service retreat in western quadrant.
收到  将军
Copy, general.
特勤局撤退的唯一原因
The only reason secret service would retreat
是他们以为总统在他们手上
is if they thought juma had the president.
但是鲍尔说他已经把我妈送进安全屋了
But that man, Bauer, said he got  my mother into the lockdown.
朱玛在虚张声势
Juma's bluffing them.
我们得从这儿出去
We need to get out of here
让大家知道这里的情况并夺回白宫
and let our people know that as soon as possible so they can retake the building
从这儿出去  怎么做  到处都是他们的人
Get out of here? How? They're everywhere.
快走
- Move it! -Shh!
把手放在头上  快走
Keep your hands on your head-- move it!
快点
Go! move it!
走  快点
Go! move!
快点  快
Move it! move!
快点
Move it!
快点  快走
Come on, move!
快点  动起来
Move it! move your feet.
出来
Get out here.
快点  快点
Move it. move it.
就是这  快点
Right here. keep going.
快点  快点
Come on. move it!
蹲下  蹲下  都蹲下
Sit down! sit down! everyone down!
都蹲下
Everyone down!
蹲下  快
Get down. down now!
蹲下  转过身去  转过去
Get down! turn around. turn around.
你能打开吗
Can you open it?
能
Yes.
要是霍奇给我们的说明书没错的话
Assuming the specifications hodges gave us are correct.
要多久
How long?
15分钟
15 minutes.
我们在一层的一个走廊里和他们正面交火
We confronted them in one of the first floor corridors.
那时  朱玛让我们撤退
At that point, Juma ordered us to retreat,
威胁说如果我们不照办的话会杀了总统
Threatening to kill the president if we didn't comply.
但我们没亲眼见到
But he never gave a visual confirmation
-总统在他手里  -没有  但我觉得
- He was holding the president? - No, he didn't, but i felt,
那时我除了撤退没别的路可走
At that point, i had no choice but to pull back.
他的人在屠杀平民和探员们
His men were killing civilians and agents.
知道现在还有多少人被困吗
Any idea how many people are still trapped inside?
比对工作人员名单和已撤离人员的姓名
Cross-checking the evacuees with the white house manifest.
到现在为止  好像是53个
So far, it looks like 53.
有特勤局的人吗
Any secret service?
据我所知 里面的探员都牺牲了
As far as I know, We have no agents left in there still alive.
人质救援小组已各就各位
Hostage Rescue Team is moving in the place.
他们已经整装待发
They'll be prepared to storm
只要一声令下他们就猛攻进去
The building as soon as the order is given.
是呀  这个节骨眼上
Yeah, well, at this point,
必须让副总统定夺了
That order has to be given by the vice president.
他在哪
What's his status?
特勤局正护送他前往一个安全的地方
Secret service has him en route To a secure location.
好的  他安全了通知我一声
All right, let me know as soon as he's locked down.
霍维斯  给我一份白宫的红外卫星扫描图
And Hovis, I need an infrared sat-scan of the building.
要最高的分辨率
Highest resolution possible.
好的
Got it.
[登记名单:  杰克·鲍尔]
Jack Bauer
你没跟我说杰克在白宫
You didn't tell me that jack was in the white house.
他是被捕了
He was under arrest.
在袭击发生时他被看管着
Being held under guard when the attack took place.
为什么被捕
Under arrest for what?
他发现了参议员迈尔的副手伯内特
He found out an aide to senator mayer named burnett
参与了这场阴谋
Was part of the conspiracy.
杰克对他逼供时被逮个正着  就在白宫里面
He was caught torturing him... In the white house.
差点要了他的性命
Almost killed the man before he was stopped.
蕾妮  你的首要任务是总统  不是杰克·鲍尔
Renee, the president is our priority, not jack bauer.
-明白了吗  -明白了
- Are we clear on that? - Clear.
-你确定  -是的
- Are you sure? - Yes.
他们正带来更多的人质
They're bringing in more hostages.
快坐下
Get down! now!
过来  坐下
Get in here! sit!
不许说话
No talking.
我没有看到奥利维亚
I don't see olivia.
是好消息啊  总统阁下
Madam president, that's good news.
我了解亚伦·皮尔斯
I know aaron pierce.
他会尽他所能  保护您的女儿
He will do everything in his power to make sure that your daughter is safe.
我的上帝  这可是白宫啊
This is the white house, for god's sake.
他们怎么通过我们的
How is it possible that they were able
重重警戒的
To get around our security protocols?
只有一种可能
There's only one explanation.
他们有内应
They had help on the inside.
是谁
From whom?
这太疯狂了
Oh, this is insane.
朱玛肯定知道他不可能活着出去了
Juma must realize that there's no way for him to get out of this alive.
恐怕是的  这是他的最后一搏
I'm afraid he does. This is his endgame.
他来这个国家是为了敲山震虎
He came here to make a statement,
而他甘愿为此牺牲
And he's willing to die for it.
当营救小组知道您没事时  就会再冲进来的
As soon as the rescue teams realize that you're secure, they'll move in.
只是时间问题
It's only a matter of time.
他在干什么
What's he doing?
-是爆炸装置吗  -不对
- Is that some kind of explosive? - no.
鲍尔
Mr. bauer?
天哪
Oh, my god.
他们有通行密码
They've got the access codes.
我必须人让那个控制面板短路
I need to get into that panel.
我能做什么吗
Is there something I can do?
把那个工具箱给我
Yeah, give me that toolbox over there.
放在桌子上
Put it on the table.
该死
Damn it.
总统阁下  把插头插进去
Madam president, plug the cord into the wall, please.
快点
Now.
好了
Okay.
将军
General.
怎么了
What's wrong?
突然坏了
It just went dead.
他们肯定是从里面把线路搞短路了
Somehow, they must have disabled the circuitry from inside.
我们用C4炸弹炸开门
Then, we'll use c4 to blow open the door.
我们必须要在11个锁眼都打洞
We'll have to drill sinkholes into each of the 11 locking rods.
太费时间了
It will take too long.
这得看钢筋有多坚固
Depending on how the steel is hardened,
C4炸药可能都不管用
C4 might not even work.
车到山前必有路
Then we'll find another way.
不可否认的是
There can be no room for doubt.
总统已成困兽
We have the president trapped.
只要我们打开那扇门  就可以名垂青史了
We open up that door, we become a part of history.
车到山前必有路
We will find another way.
请讲
Yes.
等一下
Just a moment.
有您的专线电话
Call came in on the dedicated uplink.
我听到了
I heard it.
是他  长官
It's him, sir.
开到免提
Put him on speaker.
将军  没想到会和你直接通话
General, didn't expect to be hearing from you directly.
我可以为你做些什么
What is it i can do for you?
我们有一个麻烦
We have a problem.
总统在安全屋里
The president is secured in the lockdown.
在下早有所料
Well, we prepared you for that possibility.
我把那个安全屋的设施说明书给你了
We gave you the specs for the locking mechanism.
他们在里面把控制面板短路了
They shorted the lock out from the inside.
请你再帮我找一个进去的方法
I need you to find me another way in.
将军  我已倾囊相助了
General, I've given you everything i have to give.
我的使命已经完成了
My part in this thing is over.
你忘记了你货物还没有到手吧
Are you forgetting that you don't have the shipment yet?
将军  我希望你言而有信
Now, general, I expect you to be an honorable man.
我们有约在先
We made a deal.
我遵守了我的承诺
We held up our end of the bargain.
把你弄进了白宫
We got you in the white house.
我希望你也能信守你的承诺
I expect you to hold up yours.
我对你的期望不感兴趣
I don't care about your expectations.
你不帮我的话  我就在货到你那里之前
You help me, or i will destroy that shipment
把它销毁
Before it ever arrives to you.
等会
Hang on.
好吧
Well...
西顿  你怎么想
Seaton, what do you think?
他真的做得出来吗
Can he do what he says?
两小时内船都不会靠岸
The shipment's not due in the port for another two hours.
他的人有的是时间 毁了它   让它报废
His men will have plenty of time to destroy it, render it useless.
将军
General?
告诉我  安全屋里还有谁
Tell me-- who else is in the lockdown with the president?
我的人看到她和另一个人进去了
My men saw her enter with another man.
我在看白宫的人员清单
Well, i'm looking at the white house manifest,
上面说  奥利维亚·泰勒
And according to this, olivia taylor
现在正在你那边
Is presently in the building with you.
总统的女儿
The president's daughter?
你确定
Are you sure?
这个系统自动记录进出人员
Their system logs everyone in and out electronically.
如果上面说她在的话  她一定在
If it says that she's in there, she's in there.
把她找到
Now, you find olivia taylor,
你就可以威胁总统开门了
And you'll get the president to open that door.
你的船会如期到达的
Your shipment will arrive as planned.
谢谢
Thank you.
看见了吗  压力
There, you see-- stress.
压力
Stress...
才是创造力之本
Is the fertilizer of creativity.
还是玩会飞镖吧
Let's play some darts.
总统的女儿就在白宫
The president's daughter is somewhere in the white house.
我们去找到她
Let's find her.
抬起头来
Raise your heads.
让我看到你们的脸
Show me your faces.
你觉得发生什么事了
What do you think's going on?
我问你话呢
I asked you a question,
布坎南先生
Mr. buchanan.
你是不是觉得我惩罚鲍尔错了
You think I made the wrong call with bauer.
你觉得我要是甩手不管
You think that if I'd signed off
他逼供莱恩·伯内特的事
On him torturing ryan burnett,
一切就都可以避免了吗
All of this could have been avoided?
参议员  你根本不知道我在想什么
You don't know what i'm thinking, senator.
她不在这
She's not here.
快去把她找出来  带她来见我
Go ahead and find her and bring her to me.
怎么了
What happened?
-你看到什么了  -那扇门有警卫看守
- What did you see? - The door's guarded.
肯定有别的出路
Well, there's got to be another way out.
这边只有三个出口
There are only three exits
但是全有人把守
To this wing, and they're all covered.
窗户全是加固封锁的  根本打不破
The windows are sealed and hardened. Unbreakable.
我必须让他们知道
We have to let them know
恐怖分子在虚张声势   我妈不在他们手中
The terrorists are bluffing; that they don't have my mother.
我们只能往外发信号
Our only option is to get a signal out.
我们可以往窗外
We can do it from the windows
-发信号  -好的  好的
- Of the residence. - Okay, okay, good.
如果我把你留在安全地带会更好点
You'll be safer if I leave you in a secure area.
我发好信号就会回来找你
I'll get the signal out and come back for you.
我不会躲在该死的通风口的  皮尔斯探员
I'm not gonna sit and hide in some damn vent, agent pierce.
女士  路途遥远
Ma'am, it is a long way,
我们可能会遭遇更多敌人
And we're probably gonna encounter more of juma's men.
太危险了
It's too dangerous.
我不管
I don't care.
我跟着你  别争执了
I'm going with you, and don't try to argue.
没时间了
We don't have the time.
好吧
Okay.
跟在我后面
Stay behind me.
莫斯探员  红外卫星扫描已经就绪
Agent moss, sat-scan's all set up here.
我们能看到一群人质  但无法分辨个体
We can see the cluster of hostages, but not the individual bodies.
能更进一步吗  让图像更清晰点
That the best they can do? They can't boost the resolution on this?
不行  长官  白宫是世界上
no, sir. The white house is one of the most
防护最好的建筑物
heavily shielded buildings in the world.
收到
Yeah, got it.
-副总统已经接通  可以通话了  -多谢
- The vice president's ready. They're initiating communication.  - thanks.
大家出去下
Give us the room.
你在和副总统通话
You're on with the vice president.
副总统阁下  我是莫斯探员
Mr. vice president, i'm special agent moss,
联邦调查局首府分部的主管
Head of the fbi's dc branch.
这是沃克探员
This is agent walker.
我收到通报了
I've been briefed on the general situation.
最新情况是什么
What are the latest facts on the ground?
没有朱玛的进一步消息
There's nothing further from general juma,
但红外扫描显示
But an infrared scan of the building
他把人质集中到
Shows he's holding the hostages in a hallway
罗斯福厅外的走廊来
Outside the roosevelt room.
对于总统来讲是个好消息
Now this is very possibly good news for the president.
解释下
Explain.
那个区域易攻难守
The area's not one of the more defensible places in the building.
战术上讲  朱玛不应该选那作为阵地
Tactically, it makes no sense for juma to have chosen it as a base.
但那地方临近安全屋
However, the area is adjacent to the ground floor lockdown,
我们知道那是总统的必经之路
Which we know the president was en route to.
你觉得总统在里面了
So, you think the president made it into the lockdown?
这是最合理的解释
That's our best explanation for him being there.
所以我们请求您
We're therefore are asking you to authorize
在朱玛攻破安全屋前  下达营救命令
The rescue operation before juma manages to penetrate the lockdown.
还有别的证据表明
Do you have any other evidence that supports your theory
总统在安全屋里面吗
That the president is in the lockdown?
他曾被要求出示总统被控制的证据
There's the fact that he couldn't produce the president
但他没能做到
When we asked him to prove that he had her.
不能还是不愿意
Couldn't or wouldn't?
你也不能确定  是吗
You can't be certain which one it is, can you?
我们确实无法断定  阁下
Certainty's not possible in this case, sir.
但这是最好的判断
We're giving you our best estimation
我们请求您批准行动
And we urge you to allow us to launch.
如果你错了呢
What if you're wrong?
如果朱玛控制了总统呢
What if juma does have the president?
如果你攻击  他会立即杀了总统的
He will kill her as soon as he realizes what you're doing.
不行动也是有风险的  阁下
Inaction has its own risks, too, sir.
如果朱玛有更多的时间来加强防卫
The more time juma has to reinforce his position,
攻占白宫和营救人质会变得更加困难
The more difficult it'll be to take the building and save lives
我明白
I understand.
但首要考虑的是总统的性命
But my priority must be the president's life.
没有更多总统的情况前
Prudence dictates that i hold off on authorizing the rescue operation
我要谨慎从事
Until we can be more certain of her status.
副总统阁下
Mr. vice president,
恐怖分子控制了白宫
Terrorists are in control of the white house.
我想问您谨慎是合理的反应吗
I would ask you to consider if prudence is the appropriate response in this situation.
沃克探员  我感谢你的建议
I thank you for your thoughts, agent walker.
除非你能提供里面更多的情况
Until you can provide me with more intel on what's going on in there,
否则你绝不能轻举妄动
You are instructed to refrain from launching any action.
及时向我通报最新情况
Keep me apprised of any further developments.
他就只管自己的前途
All he's interested in is covering his own ass.
他是副总统
He's the vice president.
现在他说了算
Right now, he's calling the shots.
您的决定是英明的  阁下
It was the right call, sir.
您没法下达一个置总统于死地
You can't order an operation that results in the president's death
而自己却平步青云的命令
And your own elevation to the job.
这在政治上是不可接受的
It would be politically untenable.
别再这样说了  德里克
Never let anyone hear you talking like that, derek.
明白吗
Understood?
遵命  阁下
Yes, sir.
天哪
Oh, god...
我的天  亚伦
Oh, my god, aaron!
他们会听到枪声
They would've heard those shots,
你必须在他们来之前发出信号
So you're going to need to get the signal out before they get back.
门后面有个安全箱
There's a security kit behind that door in the bureau.
有急救设备和手电筒
It's got first aid and a flashlight.
你去窗口闪摩斯码
You'll flash morse code out the window.
摸下我夹克  那有只笔
Reach in my jacket. i got a pen.
这
Here.
给我
Give it to me.
把手伸过来
Give me your hand.
这是"绿色代码"
This is called "code green."
一点表明短闪烁  一横表示长闪烁
A dot is a short blink; a dash is a long one.
"绿色代码"就是暗示  让他们行动
"code green" will signal them to move in.
快去
Go!
朱玛将军
General juma,
我抓到总统女儿了
I have the president's daughter.
带上他
Bring him.
消息人士称40分钟前
Sources have confirmed that the siege inside the white house
白宫已经被包围
Began approximately 40 minutes ago.
我们还没得知  到底有多少名人质
We do not yet have confirmation On the number of hostages being held,
或者总统是否已落入敌手
Or if the president is among them.
我身后  可以看到几支特警队正在待命
Behind me, you can see dozens of tactical assault units standing by.
政府分析师告诉我们  攻击命令的下达
Government analysts tell us the order to launching to cut out
在当前局势下  完全取决于副总统
In these circumstances would rest with the vice president.
将军  我发现在吊灯里有光纤摄像头
General, i discovered fiber-optic cameras embedded in the chandelier.
坐下
Sit!
给我张椅子
Get me a chair.
遵命  将军
Yes, general.
他发现摄像头了
He spotted the cameras.
给我条安全通话线路
Give me a secure channel.
讲吧  长官
Go ahead, sir.
泰勒总统
President taylor,
我知道你看得见
I see now that you've been watching us.
好
Good.
我想让你看一样东西
There is something else i think you should see.
上帝啊  不要
God, no.
如果你不开门
If you don't open the door,
我会一只一只地把你女儿眼睛挖出来
I'm going to cut out your daughter's eyes one by one.
然后我会把她舌头割掉
And then i'm going to cut out her tongue...
接着是她的头
...and then her head.
妈  别听他的
Mom, don't listen!
我知道你的想法
I know what you're thinking.
怎么能保证开门后我就不杀她呢
How do you know if you open the door that i won't kill her?
但你只需要知道
All you need to know
如果你不开门  她就死定了
Is that i most certainly will kill her If you don't.
开门
Open the door.
-总统阁下  我不能  -开门
- Madam president, i can't!  - no. open the door.
-把门打开  -我不能
- Open the door!  - i can't!
我女儿在外面
That is my daughter out there.
你明白吗
Do you understand?
我已经失去了儿子
I've already lost my son.
你知道丧子之痛的痛苦吗
Have you any idea what it's like to lose a child?
总统阁下  我真的很抱歉
Madam president, i am genuinely sorry,
但我不能让他们抓到你
But i cannot let them take you.
你现在帮不了她
There is nothing you can do for her now.
你有孩子吗  杰克
Do you have children, jack?
有个女儿
I have a daughter.
你能做到你要求我的吗
Could you do what you're asking me to do?
站在这看着她被杀害
Just stand by and watch her butchered?
不能  阁下
No, ma'am.
但我不是美国总统
But i am not the president of the united states.
我是总统
Well, i am the president.
我命令你打开门
And i am ordering you to open that door.
你没时间了
You're running out of time.
妈
Mom...
也许这会让你妈早做决定
Perhaps this will make your mother decide more quickly.
妈  你不应该
Mom, you shouldn't have...
亲爱的  我不会让他们伤害你
I wouldn't let them hurt you, darling.
该死  鲍尔
Damn it, bauer.
你都做了些什么
What have you done?!
好了  将军  你抓到我了
All right, general, you've got me now.
没必要还抓着他们
There's no reason to hold anyone else.
让他们走
Let them go.
你
You...
别对我指手划脚
Don't give orders to me.
把镜头准备好  让她读声明
Get the camera ready for her statement.
什么声明
What statement?
你的最后一次声明
The last one you would ever give.